PAULINA LE

• Full-Stack Developer •

EXPERIENCE

General Assembly | Remote

SEI Instructional Associate 02/2022 - present

- Provides in course support and guides students through the development of real world projects and applications
- Assists with lectures and questions covering a wide range of in demand technologies, such as Javascript, React.js, and Node.js, Python, and more **SEI Teaching Assistant** 01/2022 present
- Leads 1-to-1 debugging and review sessions of software development concepts, such as DOM Manipulation, hoisting, and more
- Supports 20+ software engineering students outside of class on daily deliverables and monthly projects

Software Engineer Fellow 10/2021 - 01/2022

- 12-weeks software development and programming immersive with 500 hours of extensive formal training
- Built and deployed 4+ functioning full-stack, front-end, and back-end applications implementing 7+ frameworks and programming languages
- Collaborated with fellow engineers to routinely debug, wireframe, and test

Corporate Fitness Works | Washington, D.C/Remote

Health Fitness Specialist 02/2019 - 02/2022

Corporate Fitness Works | Feb 2019 - Feb 2020

- Assisted in managing 3 DOJ fitness centers and monthly BOD reports
- Created and led 25+ group exercises classes and videos per month

PROJECTS

Netflixify | MERN Stack

Deployed App

Software Engineer 01/2022

- Individually engineered and designed a full-stack application for users to create customized playlist for Netflix movies and shows
- Implemented unogsNG and uNoGS APIs to allow users to search over 17000 Netflix movies and shows across 38 countries

DevXchange | MERN Stack

Deployed App

Git Manager & Software Engineer 12/2021

- Collaborated on a team of three developers to create an open forum application to connect developers and engineers of all expertise levels
- Maintained the state of two repos by handling and merging incoming pull requests appropriately

Heavy Things Tracker | PEN Stack

Deployed App

Software Engineer 11/2021

- Independently designed and built a full-stack CRUD application where users can save exercises and log details on completed workouts
- Utilized Exercisedb and Cloudinary APIs to allow users to search over 1300 exercises and upload workout photos

CONTACT

(703-577-6528

paulinal3@outlook.com

in linkedin.com/in/paulinal3

github.com/paulinal3

paulinale.herokuapp.com

PROFILE

I am a full stack software developer who strives to provide efficient and functional products. I am passionate about using technology to create a healthy space for users. My previous experience as a personal trainer has given me a creative outlook on how to approach different challenges and the patience to find effective solutions.

SKILLS

- JavaScript/ES6
- HTML5
- CSS/Bootstrap
- React.js
- Node.js/Express
- Python
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- Version Control

EDUCATION

Certificate - Software Engineering Immersive General Assembly

Oct 2021 - Jan 2022

Bachelor of Science - Human Nutrition, Foods and Exercise Virginia Tech

Aug 2014 - May 2018